{
  "wrapper": "div#faq",
  "sections": {
    "faq-form": {
      "type": "faq-form",
      "blocks": {
        "d8d1e281-78e7-434b-857f-c52500e3debe": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Top Questions",
            "slug": "top-questions"
          }
        },
        "2a2232a4-320c-40f7-bfbf-feae37356318": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Trials, Returns and Refunds",
            "slug": "trials-returns-and-refunds"
          }
        },
        "10221e63-0386-457f-a5f6-ce221a687644": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Financing",
            "slug": "financing"
          }
        },
        "abf9e6ea-2e4a-4098-8fb4-ee300a9ada74": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Warranty",
            "slug": "warranty"
          }
        },
        "5ef6b5c6-0074-4e3d-9952-c09ccadd37e6": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Order",
            "slug": "order"
          }
        },
        "8b466142-1c45-4250-b392-700bccc74925": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Shipping",
            "slug": "shipping"
          }
        },
        "3093edb9-24a7-4e98-a063-ac3031ccafda": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "CliMax Hybrid",
            "slug": "emma-climax-hybrid"
          }
        },
        "2282f61e-b3a8-4829-a4f4-19079b2d9134": {
          "type": "qna-button",
          "settings": {
            "title": "Emma Original",
            "slug": "emma-original"
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "d8d1e281-78e7-434b-857f-c52500e3debe",
        "2a2232a4-320c-40f7-bfbf-feae37356318",
        "10221e63-0386-457f-a5f6-ce221a687644",
        "abf9e6ea-2e4a-4098-8fb4-ee300a9ada74",
        "5ef6b5c6-0074-4e3d-9952-c09ccadd37e6",
        "8b466142-1c45-4250-b392-700bccc74925",
        "3093edb9-24a7-4e98-a063-ac3031ccafda",
        "2282f61e-b3a8-4829-a4f4-19079b2d9134"
      ],
      "settings": {
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-1": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How can I track my order?",
            "answer": "<p>Right after purchasing your Emma product, please wait for a confirmation email indicating your product tracking number and instructions on how to track your order.  <br\/><br\/>For easy tracking, here's a quick <a href=\"https:\/\/www.emma-sleep.com\/a\/order-status\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"Order status\">link<\/a> where you can track your order using your Email address and Order Number. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "What are the dimensions of your mattresses?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Emma Mattresses come in 6 sizes– find one that suits you!<br\/><br\/><strong>Twin: 38” x 75”<\/strong><\/p><p>- Best for children, teens, or anyone under six feet tall.<br\/><strong>Twin XL: 38” x 80”<\/strong><\/p><p>- Best for growing children and\/or teens.<br\/><strong>Full: 54” x 75” <\/strong><\/p><p>- Best for individuals or couples looking for something compact yet <br\/><strong>Queen: 60” x 80” <\/strong><\/p><p>- Best for individuals or couples who want extra space.<br\/><strong>King: 76” x 80” <\/strong><\/p><p>- Best for families who sleep together.<br\/><strong>California King: 72” x 84”<\/strong><\/p><p>- Best for maximized space and comfort for your family and even pets<br\/><br\/>If you’re still undecided on what size to get, we’d be more than willing to help you out.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How long does shipping take?",
            "answer": "<p>Our free shipping takes approximately 2-5 business days nationwide. Aside from free shipping, we do offer a scheduled delivery option complete with in-home set up in selected areas within the US for a small fee starting from $69 up to $129. If your area is covered, you can avail of this service and choose a date of when to receive your Emma!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "d90c6322-ab2a-4e2e-8461-84f2032b0f36": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can I schedule my delivery in advance?",
            "answer": "<p>We do have a scheduled delivery option for selected areas within the US for a small fee of $69 to $129. Simply reach out to us to confirm if your shipping address is within our serviceable areas. Outside of this, you can expect to receive your mattress within 2-5 business days of placing your order.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "e7775e0b-6848-453d-a828-59457dab4550": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Do you ship nationwide?",
            "answer": "<p>We do offer free shipping within the contiguous United States. <br\/>At present, these are our non serviceable territories: <br\/> • Alaska<br\/> • Hawaii<br\/> • Puerto Rico<br\/> • US Virgin Islands<br\/> • American Samoa<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "4d90585e-e967-45de-a14b-9688f25a3734": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How does your 365 Night Trial work?",
            "answer": "<p>Our risk-free 365-night trial means that you get a year to decide if your Emma mattress is a good fit for you. This gives you more time to try the mattress for yourself and experience the benefits that our 4Million+ customers have come to enjoy every night!<br\/><br\/>Helpful Tip: We recommend you sleep on your Emma for at least 21 nights so that you and your body can get suited to your new Emma mattress.<br\/><br\/>You can begin your 365-night trial today. Our 0% APR financing with Klarna also gives you the option to make 12 equal payments over the next 12 months.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "fc3c40f1-b4aa-4211-b763-bb1e08b07298": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How Firm is your Emma Original?",
            "answer": "<p>The Emma Original Mattress is considered ‘Medium Firm.' Our experts have concluded that this is the firmness level suitable for most types of sleepers, as it offers the right balance of pressure relief and support. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "9a71c11f-0222-4a98-b6b6-2f5f9fd57ccb": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How can I cancel or return my order?",
            "answer": "<p>We at Emma know that returns should be both conveient and simple! For any cancellation or returns questions. Please feel free to connect with us via our channels below available 24\/7<br\/><br\/>Email: support@emma-sleep.com<br\/>Landline: +1-888-580-3662<br\/><br\/>or speak directly with an agent using the live-chat feature on our website, available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "b09bdf7b-9096-4c92-80a0-7f32e721817a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Do you have a physical store so I can try out the mattress?",
            "answer": "<p>At the moment, our products are only available online at www.emma-sleep.com<\/p><p> <br\/>However, we do offer a generous 365 nights risk-free trial period so you can try out the mattress from the comfort of your home, and if you feel that Emma isn't a perfect match for you, simply reach out to us, and we'll process your return - and give you a full refund. No need to pay any shipping charges as well.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "9fad6ba2-a12c-42ce-8b36-443a62dc06da": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can I use multiple discount codes?",
            "answer": "<p>Unfortunately, we can only accommodate the use of one discount code per transaction (i.e. no stacking of discount codes). <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "f390c1b0-7236-45cd-a75a-cbacc8d177cd": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How do I take care of my Emma mattress?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Emma mattresses come with a removable and washable cover. Simply open the zipper and separate the top from the bottom part. Wash the cover while maintaing a temperature below 140°F in the washing machine. You can also wash single stains by hand with gentle washing detergent.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "652dd428-43ca-4e34-964e-35421a8894ab": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How can I contact Emma Customer Support?",
            "answer": "<p>We look forward hearing from you! For any questions or help needed, feel free to contact us via our channels below!<br\/><br\/>Email: support@emma-sleep.com<br\/>Landline: +1-888-580-3662<br\/><br\/>or speak directly with an agent using the live-chat feature on our website which is available is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "d90c6322-ab2a-4e2e-8461-84f2032b0f36",
        "e7775e0b-6848-453d-a828-59457dab4550",
        "4d90585e-e967-45de-a14b-9688f25a3734",
        "fc3c40f1-b4aa-4211-b763-bb1e08b07298",
        "9a71c11f-0222-4a98-b6b6-2f5f9fd57ccb",
        "b09bdf7b-9096-4c92-80a0-7f32e721817a",
        "9fad6ba2-a12c-42ce-8b36-443a62dc06da",
        "f390c1b0-7236-45cd-a75a-cbacc8d177cd",
        "652dd428-43ca-4e34-964e-35421a8894ab"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Top Questions",
        "slug": "top-questions"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-2": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How does your 365-Night-Trial work?",
            "answer": "<p>Our risk-free 365-night trial means that you get a full year to decide if your Emma mattress is a good fit for you. This gives you more time to try the mattress for yourself and experience the benefits that our 4Million+ customers have come to enjoy each night!<br\/><br\/>Helpful Tip: We recommend you sleep on your Emma for at least 21 nights so that you and your body can get suited to your new Emma mattress.<br\/><br\/>You can begin your 365-night trial today. Our 0% APR financing with Klarna also gives you the option to make 12 equal payments over the next 12 months.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Do I need to keep the plastic on the mattress while I'm on the free trial?",
            "answer": "<p>No need! You can enjoy our Emma mattresses as you normally would any mattress. If you wish to return it later on, simply reach out to us and we'll take care of the rest!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Am I going to receive a full refund within my night trial?",
            "answer": "<p>Definitely! With our 365-night risk-free trial, we will refund you the full amount should you choose to return your Emma; you won't even need to pay any shipping charges! <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "d90c6322-ab2a-4e2e-8461-84f2032b0f36": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Is it free to return your products?",
            "answer": "<p>It's 100% free to return your Emma! If your Emma turns out not to suit you for any reason, feel free to return it. Just simply get in contact with us via our chat support, phone or email  and we will refund and collect it at no cost to you.<\/p><p><\/p><p>Live support is also available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "a47229ea-227c-458d-a8eb-70349824fc51": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "What condition can I return the mattress in?",
            "answer": "<p>Emma products that are to be returned must be in donable condition to be eligible for return (e.g., no significant stains, tears or other soiling including odors). To know more information, you may view our terms & conditions (Article VIII) <a href=\"\/pages\/terms-and-conditions\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"Terms and Conditions\">here<\/a>. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "bb7fb70e-173c-4173-8602-4fe5cc9d61b3": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Is the 365-Night trial applicable for all products?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Emma mattresses come with a 365-night risk-free trial. As for our other Emma products, most come with a generous 60-night risk-free trial, except for the Wooden Bed Frame and the Adjustable Powerbases. You can see the breakdown for trials and warranties below.<\/p>",
            "html": "<table class=\"table-fixed border-collapse border border-black\">\n      <thead>\n        <tr>\n          <th class=\"w-1\/3 p-2 md:p-4 font-bold border border-black\">Product<\/th>\n          <th class=\"w-1\/3 p-2 md:p-4 font-bold border border-black\">Risk Free Trial Nights<\/th>\n          <th class=\"w-1\/3 p-2 md:p-4 font-bold border border-black\">Warranty<\/th>\n        <\/tr>\n      <\/thead>\n      <tbody>\n        <tr>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">Emma Mattress<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">365 Nights<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">10 Years<\/td>\n        <\/tr>\n        <tr>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">Pillows<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">60 Nights<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">3 Years<\/td>\n        <\/tr>\n        <tr>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">Protectors<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">60 Nights<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">3 Years<\/td>\n        <\/tr>\n        <tr>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">Power Base and Power Base Pro<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">NA<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">10 Years<\/td>\n        <\/tr>\n        <tr>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">Wooden Bed Frame<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">NA<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">1 Year<\/td>\n        <\/tr>\n        <tr>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">Upholstered Bed Frame<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">60 Nights<\/td>\n          <td class=\"p-2 md:p-4 text-center border border-black\">5 Years<\/td>\n        <\/tr>\n      <\/tbody>\n    <\/table>"
          }
        },
        "0ba70c52-b549-4aed-858d-d0ab3ce51c57": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I have returned my Emma product, when will I receive my refund?",
            "answer": "<p>Thank you for cooperation with our returns process! After we have confirmed that you returned your Emma products, you can expect your full refund through your original payment method within 5-10 business days. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "973c1117-6633-44b4-a37e-db8ab1fad173": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "What is the difference between trial period vs warranty?",
            "answer": "<p>Our 365-Night Trial is a period where you can try our Emma products for a whole year, and at any time choose to return it if you think it is not suited for you.<br\/><br\/>Our 10-Year warranty on the other hand is your assurance of getting a replacement if damage existed prior to use, and if this was a result of production or faulty workmanship\/materials which are not attributable to transportation.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "d90c6322-ab2a-4e2e-8461-84f2032b0f36",
        "a47229ea-227c-458d-a8eb-70349824fc51",
        "bb7fb70e-173c-4173-8602-4fe5cc9d61b3",
        "0ba70c52-b549-4aed-858d-d0ab3ce51c57",
        "973c1117-6633-44b4-a37e-db8ab1fad173"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Trials, Returns and Refunds",
        "slug": "trials-returns-and-refunds"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-4": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can you explain the Emma Mattress 10-year warranty?",
            "answer": "<p>We got your back 100%. The 10-year warranty begins as soon as you receive your Emma mattress, and it covers damages caused by factory defects and\/or faulty materials. For more information please check our <a href=\"\/pages\/terms-and-conditions\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"Terms and Conditions\">Terms and Conditions<\/a>.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Will I always get a similar product model as my replacement due to a warranty claim?",
            "answer": "<p>We guarantee that we will replace your Emma product with the same model as long as it is available. Otherwise, we will replace your mattress with a current model that is the same, or greater in value. *<br\/><br\/>*Terms and Conditions may apply<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I received my Emma as a gift. Am I still eligible for the 10 year warranty?",
            "answer": "<p>If your Emma was given as gift, you can simply get in touch with us and share the following to have your warranty processed:<br\/><br\/>- Proof of purchase<br\/>- Authorization from the purchaser that allows you to inquire about the order - this can be a form of a call or email from the purchaser.<br\/><\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "9c888ebb-db60-465a-baf1-56b732013590": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I bought my Emma from a different shop. Am I covered with the 10 year warranty?",
            "answer": "<p>Unfortunately, only Emma products that were purchased in the US and through our official website are covered by our warranty. For more information, please check our <a href=\"\/pages\/terms-and-conditions\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"Terms and Conditions\">Terms and Conditions.<\/a><\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "9c888ebb-db60-465a-baf1-56b732013590"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Warranty",
        "slug": "warranty"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-3": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "What are the payment options available?",
            "answer": "<p>You may pay via any major credit and debit card, digital wallets, and also various installment options through our website! <\/p><p><\/p><p>We accept: Visa, Mastercard, American Express, Discover, Diners Club, PayPal, Apple Pay, Google Pay, MetaPay, ShopPay, Klarna, and Koalafi.<br\/><br\/>You can also pay in installments through Klarna and ShoPay! For lease-to-own options, you can pay via Koalafi.<br\/><\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can I pay for the mattress in installments?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes you can! Our financial partners Klarna & ShopPay offer flexible, interest-free payments: you can choose either our pay-in-4 option, or our monthly installments option of up to 12 months. Learn more about your financing options with Klarna by clicking on this <a href=\"\/pages\/financing\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"Financing\">link<\/a>.<br\/><br\/>If you have more questions, you can reach Klarna anytime through their customer service. Visit this <a href=\"https:\/\/www.klarna.com\/us\/customer-service\/\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"Customer Service | Klarna US\">link<\/a> to get in touch with them via chat or call.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "4aef76d5-b857-42bf-acb1-cf9ba26c9393": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "What other financing options are available?",
            "answer": "<p>For our customers building credit, we offer lease-to-own financing with Koalafi. With a lease, you can split the cost into regular rental payments, and you have the option to pay off early to save. Learn more via this <a href=\"https:\/\/www.emma-sleep.com\/pages\/koalafi-financing\">link<\/a>. For questions, call Koalafi’s customer support team at 844-937-8275.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How can I get in touch with Klarna?",
            "answer": "<p>Klarna is available 24\/7. You can reach them any time via chat or call through the following <a href=\"https:\/\/www.klarna.com\/us\/customer-service\/\" target=\"_blank\" title=\"https:\/\/www.klarna.com\/us\/customer-service\/\">link<\/a>. Just head on over to their customer service. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "e1a2d5a1-b476-447e-abda-790d27512cf2": {
          "type": "qna",
          "disabled": true,
          "settings": {
            "question": "How can I get in touch with Koalafi?",
            "answer": "<p>For customers building credit, we offer lease-to-own financing with Koalafi. Learn more via <a href=\"https:\/\/www.emma-sleep.com\/pages\/koalafi-financing\">this link<\/a>. For questions, call their customer support number at 844-937-8275 between 8:00am and 9:00pm ET Monday through Friday, or 8:00am to 8:00pm ET on Saturday.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "192e9434-1eb2-4162-a7ec-c33ec729829c": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I bought my Emma via Klarna financing. Can I still return my product?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, you definitely can! All Emma mattress purchases are eligible for our free trial, free shipping & returns, and 10-year warranty.<br\/><br\/>If you need to return a part of or your full order, Klarna will issue you with a new statement. Simply log into your Klarna account, select “report a return”, and Klarna will pause your statement.<br\/><br\/>Then just reach out to our Emma Customer Support Team and they'll assist you with the returns and refunds process. Once Emma processes your return, Klarna will send an adjusted invoice.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "be60e744-a75a-4bd1-ba3a-d87b8bcebf84": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I bought my Emma mattress via Koalafi financing. Can I still return my product?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, you definitely can! All Emma mattress purchases are eligible for our free trial, free shipping & returns, and 10-year warranty. Contact our Emma Customer Support Team and they’ll assist you with the returns and refunds process.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "4aef76d5-b857-42bf-acb1-cf9ba26c9393",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "e1a2d5a1-b476-447e-abda-790d27512cf2",
        "192e9434-1eb2-4162-a7ec-c33ec729829c",
        "be60e744-a75a-4bd1-ba3a-d87b8bcebf84"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Financing",
        "slug": "financing"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-5": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "What is my order number?",
            "answer": "<p>Your order number can be found in the email confirmation sent after completing the checkout process. Alternatively, you can find it in the Emma order page summary.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "My bank was charged with my order but I didn’t get an order confirmation email, can you please check my order?",
            "answer": "<p>For us to check your order and the charge, kindly contact our Customer Care Team through our available channels:<br\/><br\/>Email: support@emma-sleep.com<br\/>Landline: +1-888-580-3662<br\/><br\/>or speak directly with an agent using our live-chat feature available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I ordered an incorrect size, can I still change my order?",
            "answer": "<p>Simply reach out to our Customer Service team and provide us your order number and email address so we can check this for you! Our live chat feature is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "a659f2ab-1fba-48fc-96f6-327c0cc4b181": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "My shipping address is incorrect and I'd like to change it",
            "answer": "<p>Simply reach out to our Customer Service team and provide us your order number and email address so we can check this for you! Our live chat feature is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "27c134d4-276a-4c79-8097-24afd9156a82": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can I pay for my order through phone?",
            "answer": "<p>For a secure and safe transaction, all Emma orders are processed  via our website at www.emma-sleep.com<br\/><br\/>Please be aware that Emma will not contact you and ask for personal or financial details to secure your order. Do not hesitate to get in touch with us if you need assistance ordering your Emma. Our Customer Service team will be glad to assist you 24\/7 via chat, phone or email. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "a659f2ab-1fba-48fc-96f6-327c0cc4b181",
        "27c134d4-276a-4c79-8097-24afd9156a82"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Order",
        "slug": "order"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-8": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "My order hasn’t arrived, can you please cancel my order?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Customer Service team will be glad to assist you via chat, phone or email. Live support is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday.<\/p><p>Kindly have your order number or email address handy for a us to quickly check your order, and we'll take care of the rest. <\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I received a wrong product, how can I get the right one?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Customer Service team will be glad to assist you via chat, phone or email. Live support is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday! <\/p><p>Kindly have your order number or email address handy for a us to quickly check your order, and we'll take care of the rest.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "I am missing some of orders, can you please update me?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Customer Service team will be glad to assist you via chat, phone or email. Live support is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday!<\/p><p>Kindly have your order number or email address handy for a us to quickly check your order, and we'll take care of the rest.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "7f020963-108d-48fa-b0e3-31fbe3afc861": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "My order is showing delivered but I did not receive it. What should I do?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Customer Service team will be glad to assist you via chat, phone or email.  Live support is available from 08:00 to 18:00 GMT-6, Monday-Friday! <\/p><p>Kindly have your order number, email address and tracking number handy for a us to quickly check your order, and we'll take care of the rest.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "7f020963-108d-48fa-b0e3-31fbe3afc861"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Shipping",
        "slug": "shipping"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-6": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How much is Emma Hybrid Comfort?",
            "answer": "<p>Our Emma CliMax Hybrid Twin starts at $730 and only $1100 for a Queen! Please watch out and take advantage of our promotion to get more savings!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Is the Emma Hybrid Comfort compatible with any kind of bed frame?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, the Emma Hybrid Comfort is compatible with most bed frames, so long as their slats are no longer than 3 inches apart. It even works with adjustable bed frames!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Do I need a Box Spring with my Emma Mattress?",
            "answer": "<p>Using a box spring is optional when using the Emma Hybrid Comfort. Our mattres is compatible with any type of bed frame; you can even lay it flat out on the floor!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "9798e4ff-d6a8-469d-95d3-213f4f6a1282": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Does the foam smell?",
            "answer": "<p>As the Emma Hybrid Comfort is a bed-in-a-box mattress, it can occasionally include a slight odor as the foam layers and new materials air out for the first time. <\/p><p><\/p><p>It uses foams certified by CertiPUR-US, which are tested to ensure a low level of VOC emissions that could affect indoor air quality. While there may be a slight odor after initially unboxing the mattress, the smell dissipates quickly and should be undetectable after a day or two.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "119dac70-f48c-4abf-b0ce-5f7f74f43b34": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Is the Emma Hybrid Comfort Vegan?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, the Emma Hybrid Comfort is 100 % vegan and does not contain any animal-based materials. Unfortunately, the mattress is inedible. The foam used to make the Emma Hybrid Comfort mattress is CertiPUR-US® and Class I (16.0.93305) of STANDARD 100 by OEKO-TEX®, which means it is suitable even for infants.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "9480d367-a64f-4361-a863-ac297aa85c36": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can I wash my Emma Hybrid Comfort Cover?",
            "answer": "<p>You can wash the UltraDry® cover of your mattress. Simply open the zip along the perimeter of your mattress to remove the cover. Wash the cover while maintaining a temperature below 140°F in the washing machine. You can also wash single stains by hand with gentle washing detergent.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "f0c83d1d-837d-4a4a-a82d-93ba62549596": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How long can my Emma CliMax stay in the box?",
            "answer": "<p>It is recommended that the Emma Hybrid Comfort mattress should be opened within four (4)weeks of receiving it so as to ensure its quality.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "61cbc526-3ba0-4ffb-8fce-76eb87353a13": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Are the foams in the Emma Hybrid Comfort CertiPUR-US Certified?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes! Our Emma Hybrid Comfort are CertiPUR-US Certified. This means that the mattress is made of non-toxic materials and is safe for use!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "9798e4ff-d6a8-469d-95d3-213f4f6a1282",
        "119dac70-f48c-4abf-b0ce-5f7f74f43b34",
        "9480d367-a64f-4361-a863-ac297aa85c36",
        "f0c83d1d-837d-4a4a-a82d-93ba62549596",
        "61cbc526-3ba0-4ffb-8fce-76eb87353a13"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Emma Hybrid Comfort",
        "slug": "emma-climax-hybrid"
      }
    },
    "faq-qa-7": {
      "type": "faq-qa",
      "blocks": {
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Is the Emma Original compatible with any kind of bed frame?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, the Emma Original is compatible with most bed frames, so long as their slats are no longer than 3 inches apart. It even works with adjustable bed frames!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Do I need a Box Spring before I can use the Emma Mattress?",
            "answer": "<p>Using a box spring is optional when using the Emma Oriignal Mattress. Our mattres is compatible with any type of bed frame; you can even lay it flat out on the floor!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Does the foam smell?",
            "answer": "<p>As the Emma Original is a bed-in-a-box mattress, it can occasionally include a slight odor as the foam layers and new materials air out for the first time. <\/p><p><\/p><p>It uses foams certified by CertiPUR-US, which are tested to ensure a low level of VOC emissions that could affect indoor air quality. While there may be a slight odor after initially unboxing the mattress, the smell dissipates quickly and should be undetectable after a day or two.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "d319e61e-fe3b-48d2-8d33-d006fcd97aa1": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Is the Emma Original Mattress Vegan?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes, the Emma Original Mattress is 100 % vegan and does not contain any animal-based materials. Unfortunately, the mattress is inedible. The foam used to make the Emma Original mattress is CertiPUR-US® and Class I (16.0.93305) of STANDARD 100 by OEKO-TEX®, which means it is suitable even for infants.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "5a97ecd9-c7c7-4c40-9a21-5c82a1a1def0": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Can I wash my Emma Original Cover?",
            "answer": "<p>You can wash the UltraDry® cover of your mattress. Simply open the zip along the perimeter of your mattress to remove the cover. Wash the cover while maintaining a temperature below 140°F in the washing machine. You can also wash single stains by hand with gentle washing detergent.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "ad81067d-935d-4b87-9418-5e6959f2fd1a": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "How long can my Emma stay in the box?",
            "answer": "<p>It is recommended that the Emma Original mattress should be opened within four (4) weeks of receiving it so as to ensure its quality.<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        },
        "bc52c65c-0d3e-4ce8-b61e-a2592bbe09da": {
          "type": "qna",
          "settings": {
            "question": "Are the foams in the Emma Original Mattress CertiPUR-US Certified?",
            "answer": "<p>Yes! Our Emma CliMax Hybrid are CertiPUR-US Certified. This means that the mattress is made of non-toxic materials and is safe for use!<\/p>",
            "html": ""
          }
        }
      },
      "block_order": [
        "004d5a00-0f69-4fe1-bebe-7b602a7ad56b",
        "0b75d455-a6ba-4bff-bf6c-abd9c621a95a",
        "66c69040-025f-48ba-9722-aa9fe5a24f94",
        "d319e61e-fe3b-48d2-8d33-d006fcd97aa1",
        "5a97ecd9-c7c7-4c40-9a21-5c82a1a1def0",
        "ad81067d-935d-4b87-9418-5e6959f2fd1a",
        "bc52c65c-0d3e-4ce8-b61e-a2592bbe09da"
      ],
      "settings": {
        "title": "Emma Original",
        "slug": "emma-original"
      }
    },
    "contact-us": {
      "type": "contact-us",
      "settings": {
        "custom_title": "Need help deciding?"
      }
    }
  },
  "order": [
    "faq-form",
    "faq-qa-1",
    "faq-qa-2",
    "faq-qa-4",
    "faq-qa-3",
    "faq-qa-5",
    "faq-qa-8",
    "faq-qa-6",
    "faq-qa-7",
    "contact-us"
  ]
}